So this is a Modified Hand To Big Toe Pose.
You can use a wall for balance.
So, beginning in Mountain Pose, feeling the roots of your feet, they being extended to the earth.
Align the spine, lift the rib cage, lift the crown of the head towards the sky.
Now, getting balance on your right foot, planting all four corners of that foot down into the earth.
And now lift up the left leg.
Now I'm noticing I need to hop a little bit forward to be able to reach this leg.
So that's fine if you do that as well.
So holding on to your big toe with your index and your middle foot, and; your, no not your index and middle foot, your, your fingers.
And then reach that leg out, draw the chest back, breathe, chin parallel to the earth.
Again, feel that strength building in through your right leg, also stretching the hamstrings of the left leg.
Stability, concentration and balance.
And gently release.